You can't say that word anymore.
I think he got put on a bomb twice in a row, right?
Didn't he get put on a bomb last night?
You know why, buddy, because you're getting...
Oh, you're getting famous.
Can't read one voice back.
You can't stand a bomb by the minute.
And I can't do that to you.
Who does have the glory hole?
Because I don't have one.
Janet, do you know where the glory hole is?
I have one.
You have one too.
We all have a glory hole.
Glory hole.
You know.
And high school.
They called me old Alexander glory hole McQueen.
Back in high school.
Muscle man. I love that guy. Where's the muscles? I saw them
Yes, Joker, thank you Joker. Yeah
You remember when you and the Indian guy you and the Indian guy were like lifting weights in the backyard
And I was like, can you guys flex and you flex for me? And like nobody flexes for me. I was really strong
Usually over the summer over the winter I usually get fat and then over the summer I get really strong. That's usually how it works
I enjoyed that I just want to thank you guys
Flex it because you guys know what I was going to do and you guys were like
You guys want me to do
Stop putting me on the big screen
Be the star of the show be that come on you're the star of my fucking show
Give me a fucking thingy
Look at his butt look at his butt look at his butt
I
Cheers
Yeah, yes, yes, yes
I know everyone's fully dressed in a hijab again a full full like you know burka, and then I'm like naked
Covered in mango oil
That's really turn nobody on right now
Don't let me go on fucking full screen.
I got bigger biceps, get them out of here, get them out of here.
Okay, so go but tell who it is and then their number
Right, I can't see you guys the panel again. Yeah, I'll put it on again. Hold on. I'm sorry
Are you seeing beta completely naked, okay, whatever show it
It is a three to number three
Psyche number six. I'm a six. Okay. I'm number six
Joker you're also the number six
Joker we're like twin sixes. We're pretty wish it Joker and I are both sixes, okay
Me's are some of one
The guy holding a gun officer guy holding a gun. I'm trippin
There's a one I'm I'm the number one
Jamie
You're one with your office number one. No, I'm seven and for Empress Janet. You are number one
as well
People seven so what's everybody in the panel? I'm seven. I said I'm seven
He's in your one, so let me see here
Don't care what he said I said
No, you're you're 10 James you're 10
Exclusive footage
on a regular layout. Why do we have to see this guy doing this?
I want to see, uh, Jamie called his titties, right?
Jamie, show your titties.
Let me get the, let me get the...
Look at how biased fucking Psyche is on this panel. It's all about the men.
Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at it.
I don't want to see fucking Joker, please.
Look at his butt. Look at his butt.
I'm not interested in drawing right now. Look.
I'm looking at this for him. I'm not looking at his butt. I'm looking at his for me
I'm gonna barf right now. That's hot. That's hot. His form is
Okay, I'm at the oil I'm gonna oil up, okay, you ain't see me
Right now, but he's doing it on the solo
I want to see Janet and
Jamie
I'm gonna stop before it starts
Janet Janet cam up Janet can you cam up?
Yeah, we need some for me like it's working or I don't want to twerk
Jamie Rose. Do you feel like twerking?
We're joking
Can someone twerk please
No, I don't know how to twerk Janet knows how to twerk
Joker's gonna do it Joker Joker's Joker's a man. He's gonna do it
Yeah, Joker go ahead. Oh my god. He's taking his pants. Okay. Oh my god
Yes, oh
Shit
Thank You Joker. Oh my god. He took down it again guys. That is a real man right there. That is a fucking real man
What's going on here this was this was the freak off
This was the big freak off that everyone was talking about boring it was
I'm the only one naked there, first of all
I mean we saw beautiful like 10 seconds like
Hair in her front of her face. I could not see anything. What is this part of it?
No, it's not it is good as a soul, but as a deodorant it's whack
That's why you have to use it every day. It's the best try it try it once
No, I don't want to try it cuz I don't want to do it every day
Cuz you just want to stink like that
No, because you smell every day. That's why you have to do it on every day
Why are you using it every day because you're smelling every day?
I like to use dawn
Don is better than Dove. I would say that too.
Don is better than Dove.
Dove is better than Dove.
Yeah, it's different and you guys who's like, let me see it.
Well, it's called the fishy issue.
I didn't see any.
What would it be?
Oh, what's the issue?
Well, if you have to wear it, do you wear it every fucking day?
That means you have an issue with your fucking bill every fucking day.
Better than me.
But do you think about everything?
It's just your nose.
Your nose.
What in the fuck is going on?
I mean, it's like.
Can we get to like
Dancing or something. I mean, what is this was the freak off? I
Don't understand. I thought it was gonna be like
Shocking and fun and what's going on here viral deodorant showdown
Dress in a hijab again a full like, you know burka and
I don't want to see that again. I mean I saw that part where she's just touching her album Janet
But what is that Janet? Come on
She did freak out. She did like twerk once but
I think I lost that clip
Let's see
And they go through just like this black light room with like all these masks and dolls and
Things spread everywhere and
It's like an art project.
They're like walking through, it's like, just glowing.
I mean, Nick, that's Nick.
That's Nick Johnson.
Nick, yeah.
So having a nice day.
I'm enjoying this coffee.
I got a few, I got a twisted tea to drink later.
So I'll start drinking maybe a four or five.
I'm having a nice uh, it's a nice day. Yeah, but I had a nice uh, nice long sleepless. I think I got winter sleep
What am I I mean? I'm just babbling. I'm sorry. I can't believe people watch my show. I mean to hope for that part
I'll play my Halloween song the show has a Halloween song
No growths there, the panels hum and the chaos spins
The norhists, the mics all crack, the spirits log in
There's no turning back, oh guests crawl out of the digital grave
Cloud chasing ghosts with drama to save and die
Father's side, the cat daddy of doom, light a candle in the livestream too
In the chat they chat my name, typing hail while they play their games
Superchats flicker like cursed coins every donor feeds the noise
past appear, whispering gossip in my ear.
They fight, they flirt, they rage, they cry.
It's content, golden reasons.
Why beat us, pan the guards, the gate?
Alexandra laughs, we sealed our fakes.
Someone's mic peaks, the lights all fade.
We dance with demons, we are ourselves men.
Algorithms taste the fear.
They feed the clips for all to hear.
You say I crashed out when no one lied to
And I thought what we had was sacred
But maybe it was just meme-coated truth
And now that I've ghosted
I finally know I glitched something real
Cause I miss you
Yeah, be the-
Hey, Alexia.
He's a thinker from the Frost and Pine
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got thru-
Thanks for watching.
So beautiful. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know what thing, you know, I don't want to say like
He got one over on me, but
He's very innocent and unassuming and it's a kind person and then all of a sudden. Oh
He's in the Canadian military. Oh
Or he was no
Now everything kind of makes sense
So easy to pull the wool over my eyes
The song still made sense though, it's kind of weird.
You know what I'm saying, these songs are going to be like, maybe like some kind of divination for some of them.
Still learning where which ones are called. They're not labeled right
Cool, but it's like I don't like, you know seeing like people put stuff through their holes in their body
He's extreme. He's he's he's he's officially
openly and
Accepting of himself of being the carnival freak show he wants to be the freak show and he's like yeah, and
It's working for him. That's that's him
No, well, it's like I
I don't know I feel I feel like him inside a lot of times. Yeah, I have thousands watch me
Just to pick my nose
Really?
I won't be watching but I get it just look away. I get it
Um, I bring you an A-list guest and you stream like a woman gaudy
Thank you
The mini man's enough they're showing her badge and shit mini man's never showed her badge in the show
She showed she just said the n-word a bunch of times
Formed on me, but I have seen her vagina or his vagina several times
In a allied master computer sends it to me when he texts me, so I don't know why he does that, but
Not me I'm shadow band again
Pro Mutual Mike then boom
Drop a baseline dirtier than the check
Smashing rafters like
Licking watch catalog somehow
Rando's rantin' bout A.I. Toons
While his playlist's all cartoons
Mason's basin' red-eyed rage
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie-
He just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic, nuclear loud
Beat the storms and turn it down
You clown!
Trony bombs the stream with skin
Chat explodes
Mods dive in
He man in time
Rogin' free
Burning bridges livin' HD
And it's all so true.
Ghost is connected.
Canada drive timed out.
Randall's still typing.
Wait, Debita just banned me.
Laughter static cat me out.
In stream.
Spread the cards by candlelight
And shake your nights to wise
The high priestess beneath mortal disguise
Moonlight veiled immortalize
Across the table
in street clothes preaching mystery and sermons of touch breaking the very vows you once imposed
the unspoken archana
she's the priestess keeper of the tide he's the hierophant gatekeeper of prize
To pass a spirit crossing lines, they drew
He taught the temple, she taught what's true
Love became a siphon, either could decode
Secrets turned sacred, sacred turned
I've seen every
She turned the veil he dropped the crown to divine liars finally bowing down
The unspoken arcana
She's the priest
Lovers who rewrote the spine of
It's the only time the mask fall off
That's when I breathe
When the static becomes on
I'm honey on your sins
Then I'm on your tongue
So what you running from baby
How's it going? Oh, I guess I had to go back and turn off the
YouTube part
Oh, you do okay
How are you? Oh
We lost her it's demonic day. Oh, well
It's I'm a demon
You're feeling you're being compelled. Well, don't come up you want
Everyone just wants to pick on me tonight.
I'll just say, I'm not feeling very good.
I just came up to say hi.
So thanks for coming anyway.